The mission was survival.
The Outpost is a war, drama, history film directed by Rod Lurie.
A small unit of U.S.
soldiers, alone at the remote Combat Outpost Keating, located deep in the valley of three mountains in
Afghanistan, battles to defend against an overwhelming force of Taliban fighters in a coordinated attack.
The Battle of Kamdesh, as it was known, was the bloodiest American engagement of the Afghan War in 2009
and Bravo Troop 3-61 CAV became one of the most decorated units of the 19-year conflict.
Staff Sergeant Clint Romesha, played by Scott Eastwood.
Specialist Ty Michael Carter, played by Caleb Landry Jones.
CPT. Benjamin D. Keating, played by Orlando Bloom.
Sgt. Armando Avalos, played by Ernest Cavazos.
Lt. Andrew Bundermann, played by Taylor John Smith.
Sergeant Vernon Martin, played by Cory Hardrict.
The Outpost is a 2019 American war film directed by Rod Lurie, based on the 2012 non-fiction book The Outpost: An
Untold Story of American Valor by Jake Tapper, about the Battle of Kamdesh in the War in Afghanistan.
It stars Scott Eastwood, Caleb Landry Jones, Orlando Bloom, Jack Kesy, Cory Hardrict,
Milo Gibson, Jacob Scipio, Will Attenborough, and Taylor John Smith.
It had its world premiere at Thessaloniki
International Film Festival on November 2, 2019.
The film was scheduled to premiere at the 2020 South by Southwest Film
Festival, but the festival was cancelled due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
It was released via Premium VOD and in selected theaters on July 3, 2020.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics, with praise for
the battle sequences and respectful depiction of the soldiers.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, afghanistan, based
on true story, afghanistan war (2001-2021), soldier.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.